A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA132
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1
  - Psychosomatic Medicine Monograph; American Society for Research, 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Quin, Barbara S., 1926 1928 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Ralli, Elaine P., 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Rains, Edith [re], 1936 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Raisbeck, Milton J., 1937-1939 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Rake, G.W., 1938 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Read, J. Marion, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Reimann, H.A., 1936 1938 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Reisinger, John A. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    See Veterans Administration.
  - Reynolds, F.P., 1936 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Reynolds, C.R., 1936 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Reinhardt, Louise, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Raisbeck, Milton J., 1928-1932 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Random House, 1928-1929 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Ranke, Hermann, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Raskob, John J., 1931 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Raushenbush, Stephen, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Ravdin, I.D., 1929 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Rector, F.L. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    See Physicians in Industry.
  - Reid, G., 1932 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Reiland, Karl, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Reiss, J.P. and Co., 1929 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Reimann, H., 1928 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Resnik, William H., 1928-1930 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Reynolds, Frederick P., 1928-1931 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Rhees, Morgan J., 1929 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Rhoads, CP., 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Rado, Emmy C., 1943 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Radunzel, Miss, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Raleigh Hotel, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Rains, Edith F., 1940 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ralli, Elaine P., 1940 1944 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ramirez, Maximilian A., 1942 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Rantz, J., 1944 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Rappleye, W.C., 1940 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ray, G.B., 1942 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Reichsman, Franjo, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Reid, James N. Mrs., 1941 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Rein, Charles R., 1941 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Resnikoff, Dr. Paul. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    See Barrett, Michael.
  - Regius Professorship of Medicine, Oxford, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Raisbeck, Milton J., 1923-1924 1926-1927 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Railson, George E., 1926 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Ratnoff, Nathan, 1924 1926-1927 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Reiman, H., 1927 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Resnik, William H., 1924 1926 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Rand, Mera, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Reis, Bernard and Co., 1949 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Rappleye, Dr. Willard (Box 31, Folder 6)
    See Research Council, Department of Hospitals.
  - Rawls, W.B. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    See Medical Society, New York County.
  - Ralli, Elaine P., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Reston, James B., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Reynolds, Victor, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Rhoads, CP., 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Radio Corporation of America, 1927-1928 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - RESEARCH COUNCIL, DEPARTMENT OF HOSPITALS
    - General, 1942 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Hospital Records and Paper Salvage Drive, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Dawson, Martin H., 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Lough, Walter G., 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Rappleye, Willard G., 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Seegal, David, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Shannon, James A., 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Steele, J. Murray, 1942 1944 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Material for annual meeting of Research Council, 26 Apr, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Bernecker, Edward M., 1943 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - "Meeting of the Scientific Committee of the Research Council...", 1944 February 23 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, Scientific Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, Research Council, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Bernecker, Edward H., 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Earle, David P. Jr., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Gregg, Alan, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Rappleye, Willard C., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Palmer, Walter W., 1945 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Note, 2 Jul, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Seegal, David, 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Steele, J. Murray, 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Agendas, Minutes, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Resignations, 1950-1951 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Riesman, David, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Ringer, M., 1927 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Rice, John L., 1940 1942 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Richards, A.N., 1942 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Richards, Miss Harriet M., 1940 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Richardson, Henry B., 1941 1945 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Riegelman, Charles A., 1944 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Riesman, David, Jr., 1942 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Rÿlant, P., 1945 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Ringer, Paul H., 1943 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Ritz Hotel, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - RIVERS, THOMAS M., 1937-1940 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    See also below.
  - RIVERS, THOMAS M., 1941-1953 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Rice, John L., 1935 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Rich, Arnold, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Richards, A.N., 1929 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Richardson, Henry B., 1928 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Rienter, Harry A., 1933 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Riesman, David, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Riggs, Austen Fox, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Riley, Henry Alsop, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Ritchie, W.L., 1932 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Rivers, T.M., 1932 1934 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Rich, Margaret E. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Richards, A.N., 1937 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Richards, Lillian M., 1938 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Riesman, David, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - ROBINSON, G. CANBY, 1928-1929 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - ROBINSON, G. CANBY, 1930-1935 1940 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - ROBINSON, G. CANBY, 1920-1922 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Robertson, O.H., 1924 1926-1927 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1923-1924 1927 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Rosenthal, Alma, 1923? 1924 1926 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Rothberger, F., 1926-1927 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Rous, Peyton, 1923-1927 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Rubinow, I.M., 1923 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Russell, Miss D.M., 1923 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Robinson, Arthur, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Robinson, G. Canby, 1951-1954 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Rodman, J.S., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Rogers, Frank B., 1952 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rose, Alfred L., 1952 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rose, Charles, Jr., 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rosen, Samuel, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rosenberg, James N., 1949 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rosenwald, Lessing, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rous, Peyton, 1946-1949 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rous, Ellen, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Russell, F.F., 1952 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Ryle, John A., 1947 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rosenthal, Morris (Box 32, Folder 10)
    See Sydenham file.
  - Rosenwald, Harold (Box 32, Folder 10)
    See under Hiss, Alger.
  - Rock, Lilian D., 1950 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rosen, Fred, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Robertson, O.H., 1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Robinson, G. Canby, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, John D., 1937? (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs., 1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Box 32, Folder 11)
    See under China Medical Board.
  - Roesler, Hugo (Box 32, Folder 11)
    See under World's Fair.
  - Rolleston, Humphry, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Romeike Press-clipping Service (Box 32, Folder 11)
    See We.
  - Europeans (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Roth, Irving R., 1936-1937 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rothblatt, (Mrs.) Alice Flexner, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rothberger, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rous, Peyton, 1937-1939 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Ruppert, George E. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    See under Columbia Grammar School.
  - Russo, Eugene, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Robertson, O.H., 1928 1932-1934 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Robinson, Victor, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller, J.D. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Correspondence concerning Dr. Gasser's appointment filed in Dr. Gasser's folder.
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. J.D., 1929 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Roesler, Hugo, 1932 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rolleston, Humphry, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Romberg, Ernst von, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rosenberq, Maya, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rosenfeld, Paul, 1929-1930 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rosenthal, Alma, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rosenthal, Louis [re], 1930 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Roth, Irving R., 1932 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rothberger, C.J., 1929 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rous, Peyton, 1928 1930-1935 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Royal College of Physicians, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rubinow, Mr. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    See University of Chicago Press.
  - Russell, F.F., 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Roberts, Eugene Augustus [re], 1942 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Robertson, Albert D., 1941-1942 1944 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Robertson, Ben, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, G. Canby, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, H.M., 1945 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, Edward, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - See also under Stokes, James B. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. J.D., 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller, Mr. and Mrs. Nelson, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rodriquez, Adele [re], 1945 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rogers, Edward S., 1940 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Eleanor (Box 32, Folder 13)
    See File No. 2.
  - Rosen, George, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rosenbach, A.S.W., 1940 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rosenman, Samuel I., 1942 1945-1946 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rosenthal, Herbert (Box 32, Folder 14)
    See under Murrow, E.R.
  - Rossbach, Mrs. Laurence, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rosenwald, Mr. William, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Roth, Grace M., 1945 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Roth, Irving R., 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rous, Peyton and Marion, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rous, Ellen [re], 1944 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Runyon, Anne V.A., 1941 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rule, Colter, 1942-1944 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Russell, F.F., 1923-1924 1926 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Saturday Review, 1936 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Sabin, F.R. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    See Confidential file.
  - Sachs, B., 1930 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Sachs, Ernest, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Sachs, Julius, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Sauter, August, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Scammon, Richard E., 1933 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Sayers, R.R. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    See mss.
  - Selz, A.K., 1932 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Severingham, W.L., 1931 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Sewall, Henry, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Seabury, Judge Samuel (Box 33, Folder 3)
    See Heidelberg pamphlet.
  - Seegal, David (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Sachs, Ernest, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - St. Lawrence, William, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Salsbury, Henry L., 1944 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Salsbury, Florine, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Salzburg, Peter (Box 33, Folder 3)
    See Assistants.
  - Samuels, Bernard, 1940 1944 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Sapieha, Virgilia, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Sarton, George [re], 1945 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Scherf, Chrisman, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Sachs, Julius, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - St. Lawrence, W.P., 1923 1927 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Salmon, Thomas W., 1923 1926 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Samojloff, A., 1922-1926 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Seegal, David (Box 33, Folder 5)
    See 1) Research Committee, Department of Hospitals 2) Sydenham Hospital.
  - Salpeter, Hugh (Box 33, Folder 5)
    See Magnes, Jonathan.
  - Sachs, Ernest and Mrs., 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Savlov, Leslie H., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Salsbury, Florine, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Salvemini, Gaetano, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Samorodin, Albert J., 1948 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Samuels, Bernard, 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Selective Service, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Scarborough Commission ca, 1949, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Schaffner, Joseph Halle, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schell, Maria M., 1937 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schick, Béla, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schleiter, H.G., 1930 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schlesinger, Bernard, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schleifor, Mrs. M., 1929 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schloss, Malcolm, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schloss, Oscar M., 1928 1932 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schönheimer, Rudolf, 1930-1932 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schridde, Herm., 1927-1928 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schubmehl, F.E. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Science Service, 1932 1935 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Scott, E.L., 1928 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Scott Stamp and Coin Co., 1934 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Scott, Evelyn fund (Box 33, Folder 8)
    See DeSilver, Margaret.
  - Schneider, Howard, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Schridde, Hermann and daughter Hertha [re], 1949 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Schuman, Henry, 1946-1948 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Schuster, M. Lincoln, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Seegal, David, 1949 1952 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Segall, Harold N. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    See Electrocardiography, Confidential file.
  - Sergeant, Elizabeth S., 1949-1950 1952 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Seidenberg, Roderick, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Schaffner, Joseph H., 1944 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schmidt, Louis, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schnulowitz, Nat (Box 33, Folder 9)
    See Atlantic Monthly.
  - Schneider, H.A., 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schoen, Eugene, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Scholz, S.B., 1940 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schreiner, W. Ralph, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schubert, Barbara, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Science Service, 1940-1943 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schnur, Sidney, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Scribners, Charles, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schwartz, Arthur, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schwartz, Bernard, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schwarz, Henry, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Sears, Roebuck, and Co., 1945 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Selznick, Irene (Mrs. David), 1945 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Sendroy, Julius Jr., 1944 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Sergeant, Elizabeth, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Seegal, David, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Selekman, B.M. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Sendroy, Julius, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Seward, James M., 1942-1943 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Seymour, Whitney, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Schmidt, Louis, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Schlossmacher, Henry, 1926-1927 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Schulze, Dr., 1927 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Schridde, H., 1922 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Scientists, Association of New York, 1945-1946 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Schroeder, Henry A., 1936-1939 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Schroeder, Henry A., 1942-1943 1945-1946 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Schroeder, Henry A., 1947-1950 1953 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Schweinburg, Fritz, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Segall, Harold Nathan, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Shapero, Morris, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Shephardson, Mrs. F.L., 1928 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Shohl, Alfred T., 1928 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Sicher, Dudley D., 1933 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Sigerist, Henry, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Simon, Robert E., 1933 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Shattuck, G.C., 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Shipley, A.E. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Shore, Benjamin (Box 33, Folder 18)
    See Rains, Edith.
  - Shryock, Richard H., 1937 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Sicher, Dudley D., 1937 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Sigerist, Henry E., 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Simms, Henry S., 1938 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Simons, Hans, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Singer, Charles, 1936 1939 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Simno, Andrea, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Shapley, Harlow (Box 33, Folder 19)
    See Science legislation.
  - Sheehan, Donal (Box 33, Folder 19)
    See Sydenham Institution.
  - Silvera, John D. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Skouras, S. (Box 33, Folder 19)
    See Papandreou, C.
  - Shock, N.W. (Box 33, Folder 19)
    See Gerontological Service.
  - Silbershein, Fanny (Box 33, Folder 19)
    See Wallach, Sidney Association.
  - Simons, Hans (Box 33, Folder 19)
    See New School for Social Research.
  - Shannon, James A., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Shapley, Harlow [re], 1946 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Sheehan, Donal, 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Sherwood, Robert, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Shuman, Shirley Nelson, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Sigerist, Henry E., 1947 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Simpson, Robert, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Singer, Charles and Dorothy, 1946 1949 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Slobodkin, Morris, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Shannon, James A. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Shapiro, Arthur, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Shedlovsky, Theodore, 1942 1945 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Shirer, William L., 1944 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Shryock, Richard H., 1941 1944 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Sigerist, Henry E., 1941 1944 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Silberschein-Hirsch, Fanny, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Silve, Dave, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Silver, Mabel I., 1943 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Simmons, James S., 1943 1945 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Simons, Hans, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Siler, J.F., 1927 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Simons, Charles E., 1927 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Singer, Charles (Box 34, Folder 1)
    See We Europeans.
  - Singer, Charles, 1930-1932 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Smetana, Hans [re], 1930 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Edric B., 1928 1930 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Rennie, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Homer W., 1932-1933 1935 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Theobald, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Upsher Co., 1928 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Cornelius M. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Smillie, Wilson C., 1948 1951 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Smith, E.B., 1947-1954 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Jeanne, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Smithwick, Reginald, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Dr. Barry C. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    See Commonwealth Fund and Irvington House.
  - Smith, Edric B., 1940-1944 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Fred M., 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Frank Fremont, 1941 1943 1945 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Homer W. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Geddes (Box 34, Folder 4)
    See Commonwealth Fund.
  - Smith, Philip E., 1940 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Theobald, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Edric B., 1926-1927 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Harrison, 1924 1926 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Smith, D.E., 1923 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Mrs. A.J., 1923 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Winford H., 1925-1927 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Smyth, Clara, 1923-1924 1927 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Barry, 1936 1939 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Homer W., 1937-1938 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Kenneth S., 1936 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Rennie, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Shirley D., 1939 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Snapper, I., 1933 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sonnenberg, Benjamin (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sommerfeld, Nicholas, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sparling, Edward J., 1948 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Spivack, S.S., 1946-1947 1951 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Spreeman, Anne, 1950 1953 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Snapper, I., and son Frits, 1941-1942 1944 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sobeloff, Isidore, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Soong, T.V., 1943 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Spiegelberg, George A., 1941 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Spreeman, Anne, 1943 1945 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Spies, C.B., 1926 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Soldiers Bonus, 1934-1935 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Stake, William and Co., 1932 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Starr, Isaac Jr., 1929 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Steele, J. Murray, 1929-1931 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stein, Fred M., 1933 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Steiner, Walter R., 1928-1929 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stephen, Karen, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stanley, Carleton, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stevens, A.R., 1931 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stevens, Henry, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stewart, Harold J., 1933 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stieglitz, Leopold, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stillman, Edgar, 1933, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stockard, C.R., 1928 1931 1935 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stocks, Percy, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Stone, Willard J., 1928 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Strong, Richard P., 1931 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Stroud, W.D., 1929 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Strouse, Solomon, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Strauss, Moses, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Strunsky, Simeon, 1928 1934 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Studebaker, J.W., 1935 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Sulzberger, Marion B., 1931 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Sutton, Lucy Porter, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Stone, Harlan F., 1935 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Stone, Harvey B., 1930 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Sulzberger, A.L. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Swift, Homer and Emma, 1924 1930-1933 1935 undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Swope, Herbert B., 1934-1935 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Szold, Mrs. Robert, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Spirometer, 1926-1927 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Stead, R.A., 1949 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Stevens, David H., 1949 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Stock, Chester, 1941-1942 1948 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Staff Meetings Jan-Apr, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Stetlin, DeWitt (Box 34, Folder 14)
    See Ehrich, W.
  - Stewart, Harold J., 1936-1939 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Stieglitz, Edward J., 1936 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Stockard, C.R., 1937 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Stoloff, Charles I., 1935-1936 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Strock, Sol (Box 34, Folder 14)
    See Heidelberg Pamphlet.
  - Sturgis, Cyrus C., 1939 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Sullivan, Mark, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Sulzberger, A.H. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Sulzberger, Marion B., 1938 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Swarthe, Hilda M. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    See World's Fair file, Miscellaneous.
  - Swartz, Philip A. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    See Democracy, Friends of.
  - Swift, Homer F., 1938 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Swope, Horace, 1938? (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Steele, J.M. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    See Research Comm., Department Hospitals.
  - Staudinger, Else (Box 34, Folder 15)
    See American Comm., Emigre scholars.
  - Stieglitz, Edward J. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    See Ageing, Club for Research on.
  - Stephens, Roderick (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Svirsky, Leon (Box 34, Folder 15)
    See Lyons, Louis.
  - Switzer, Mary (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Szent-Györgyi (Box 34, Folder 15)
    See Oxford University Press.
  - Stake, William and Co., 1951 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Simons, Hans, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Staudinger, Hans, 1947 1950 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Staudinger, Else, 1949 1953 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Stein, Fred M., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Steinbrink, Meier, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Sterne, Maurice, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Stettheimer, Ettie, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1953 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Stewart, Harold J., 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Stieglitz, Leopold, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Straus, Mrs. Donald B., 1946 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Swiss Foundation, American-, for Scientific Exchange, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Swope, Herbert B., 1946-1948 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard Jr., 1949 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Swift, Homer F. dinner, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Straight, Eric W., 1945 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Standard Oil Co. of New Jersey, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Stanley, Carleton, 1944-1945 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Staudinger, Else, 1943-1944 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Staudinger, Mrs. Hans (Box 34, Folder 17)
    See folder for cross-references.
  - Steinberg, Mita, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Stern, Bernhard J., 1945 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Stern, Newton S., 1942 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Steichen, Kate Rodia, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Stettin, De Witt, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 17)